I want to try something tonight doesn't
always work but I want to try and make a
correlation if you have a job where you
work with customers every day and
there's a specific thing that a lot of
people do every day that you can't stand
what is your job and what is that thing
what I'm trying to do is Heal the World
one Comedy Club at a
time but just spreading some empathy
sort of on on both sides of the counter
so if you are comfortable sharing uh
what is it that you would tell the world
so you don't have to deal with it
anymore
well one of mine is the person who won't
turn their phone
[Applause]
off it's okay this will be on the
internet
forever
yes I don't like it when the woman says
I'd rather be at the
dentist I don't want to guess what kind
of doctor you are
all right anyone not wearing a red shirt
what is it that you
do n people will push a button to make a
beeping noise to tell me something else
is beeping that I can already
hear every day did you say every day
every day yeah there's there's a there
was years behind
that s does every day
so they call you into a room with a
beeper it's not even a room it's an open
room where I can hear beeping
everywhere I mean are you a nurse in a
casino what's
happening I mean they clearly need them
I've seen the oxygen
tanks so it's more of like an open
waiting area they hear a beeping
somewhere in the building and they get
you and they're like there's there's a
beeping yeah all right it's probably
just this guy who didn't turn his phone
on oh you you sir yeah yeah what do you
do I drive a semi all right boy okay I
have something for
you you first more the world to know we
are very slow when you're getting on the
freeway I get that okay yeah that is
Fair did everyone hear that semis are
slow when they're getting on the freeway
how about all of us make an
agreement that we will be more
patient if you
guys if you can promise that if there's
only two lanes on my side of the highway
you stick to the one is that okay
we'll shake on it afterward I don't know
what's happening were the one and it's
always right when I'm coming up one it's
like hold on just just give me 27
minutes
uh I'm so much faster than this guy I
just he's been in front of me all
day this is going to save me two minutes
getting to Walmart so
work at the creary on n9th you work at
the creary on 9th he's very this is
pointed all right so what is it that
people do though they ask me what my
favorite flavor is but I'm Dairy
intolerant
[Applause]
why do you work there what sort
of self-loathing
imagine going up to a zookeeper like
excuse me what's what's your favorite uh
mammal in here and he's like I'm
blind can't enjoy any of this
so what do you do I there's only two
choices right either you just pick a
random popular flavor or you look them
in the face and you're like how dare
you not all those were born with an iron
stomach yeah what do you do back there
uh I work at Pizza Pie Cafe pizza pie
cafe on what street
that's uh I think I've been there before
there's there's Pizza and Pasta and
other stuff and you just go up and and
ask for it or grab it like buffet style
so what is it that people do telling me
how to do my job like how I'm cooking
pasta and they're like that's not how
you do
it I hope you shoot back with something
like if you could cook pasta you'd
probably be cooking pasta right now at
home oh all right yeah let's try and get
one more these are great yeah I'm a dent
Hy oh
sorry no Hy hygienists are cool
hygienists do the dirty work and they
get paid less and then the dentist just
comes and he's like yeah that's
fine I'm going to
golf all right so what is it that we can
do better when we come in to the dentist
well everyone lies about how much they
cost
yeah I
mean that's like being heckled by a call
back to a joke
yeah that's exactly what I was saying
yeah that someone right there yeah what
do you do I'm a nurse you're a nurse
undisclosed Hospital what's up at an
undisclosed Hospital an undisclosed
hospital she's like I don't know what
these gen Z folk are doing giving out
their addresses
and yeah so what what can uh H does not
stand for hotel and RN does not mean
refreshments and
[Music]
narcotics you've said this
before I guess I've been using hospitals
wrong what what what is that did someone
hear
that what is that
beeping could you please turn that
off I'm serious though like with the
with the sound grew are we good do I
have to start at the beginning has that
been
happening the entire time
[Music]
[Applause]
all right but this time around the OBG
YN can just keep it to himself